I mister heart the news about this new
car insurance plan which is called Passed
Drive
[Music]
what is this the concept is you
pay as much as you need, African
right as much as you need recharge,
remember the days when you recharge your phone and now
this is not unlimited, always you get
serious after 100 minutes, I am of the
exact same concept now
your car has
two different models, one is the
model which is app based model where when you take car
insurance and you
download the app of the policy team, then
your policy will start running normally in it,
when you do not need it, you turn it off, if there is no
need, then turn it on,
if you are going out for 2 days, if you are
going on a holiday from your city for 4 days, then
you just turn it off and leave the
car in the range of any damage at that time
and if the car gets stolen
then your cover will still be there, the
second concept is that you know that your
car has a limited number of kilometers, then
why do you spend money on that, answer
policy market pe aake plan ki cheez karte hain, then
you  You will have to express your vehicle
and autometry
5000 km, 7500 km, 10 thousand km, the
more kilometer packages you will take, the more it will
cost you, so
you said that brother, the mains runs only 2500 km
and give it to me, like after 6 months
you can recharge it and buy it,
my take is MP + new, which should be a
product, I think everyone should buy this product,
if you use your car,
suppose you take metro or
carpolice, there are many such
ideas, it is good for tuition also, the
second option is that if you have a second car,
it is going out on weekends
or it is running six times a month, 10 times, then
why would you take that coverage for it, for
a five day to a week car,
you should take a limited number of
kilometers for it or for on-off insurance,
which is the same, so you can take many on the second
rarely used car, if you are doing business at home
and the usage of your car is only
two-three days in the whole month  I
want a limited number of films, please, you can get
it anywhere, 30% less, you can get it,
so I think everybody should buy your
plan because they are safe, you will not say anything
further, everybody else, you will actually go,
plans are live and ready on call, Shiva
[Music]